tupperware.com 2015-11-03

# Tupperware: Help > Privacy, Security & Accessibility

The privacy policy set forth below applies to Tupperware's Web sites, authorized My.Tupperware(SM) Consultant Web sites, and other authorized sales and marketing activities conducted in Canada. Please read Tupperware's privacy policy to understand how we'll handle your personal information as you take advantage of the many activities and programs offered by Tupperware: through this Web site, authorized My.Tupperware(SM) Consultant Web sites, our Tupperware Showcases located at local area shopping malls, our Tupperware offerings on television, and our traditional Tupperware Parties where you have the opportunity to shop in the convenience of your home or office with the expert assistance of your personal Tupperware Consultant.

## We're Committed to Safeguarding Your Privacy

Tupperware is a company committed to people and service. We respect your right to privacy. We believe that your personal information, including your purchases, e-mail address, billing and shipping addresses, telephone numbers, and credit card information, belongs to you. We will use this information to complete your purchases. We want to use this information to make your encounter with us more informative, and to tell you about the wonderful products and opportunities available with Tupperware. If you prefer we not customize our Web sites for you, or contact you, we provide opportunities to avoid this.

## What We Collect, How We Use It, and How You Can Opt Out

While Visiting a Tupperware Showcase, Responding to a Tupperware Television Offer, or Attending a Tupperware Party

Collection - If you have visited one of our exciting Tupperware Showcases or displays at a nearby shopping mall or retailer, responded to one of our television offers or attended one of our informative Tupperware Parties, you may have purchased our products. You may also have participated in a contest, sweepstakes, or other event, expressed an interest in receiving additional information about Tupperware® brand products, hosting a Tupperware Party, or pursuing the Tupperware Opportunity as a means of earning additional income. If so, we may have asked for your name, billing and shipping addresses, e-mail address, telephone numbers, and credit card information (type, number, expiration date). We may also have collected the purchase information (date, amount, and products).

Use - Information provided in a purchase will be used to complete the transaction using normal retail methods. Information provided in a purchase or in a request for information will also be used to contact you with news of our products and opportunities for extra income. If you have requested information on the Tupperware Opportunity and becoming a Consultant, we will forward your information to one of our Distributors so they may contact you to fulfill your request. Your information may also be combined with the information of others in an aggregated basis, without personally identifying information. This combined information may be used by Tupperware or a third party to guide us in improving our products and services (including our Web sites and catalogs), or for general business purposes (such as forecasting production).

To Opt Out - Your Consultant or Tupperware may contact you regarding your request for more information. If you have changed your mind, simply tell us and we will use all reasonable efforts to remove your information from our files and will take appropriate measures to advise your Tupperware Consultant regarding your request. In any of our e-mails you receive from Tupperware or a Consultant, there will be instructions for unsubscribing from our contact list. If you ask to be removed, you will be.

## While Visiting Tupperware.ca or Authorized Consultant Web sites

The following applies to our Web site, http://www.tupperware.ca and our authorized Consultant Web sites, which all begin with My.Tupperware.ca. These are the only authorized Tupperware Web sites available to the public.

Collection - Our Web sites include the ability for you to purchase products and/or services online. When you make a purchase, we ask for your name, billing and shipping addresses, e-mail address, telephone numbers and credit card information (type, number, and expiration date). We may also ask you to provide your Consultant's I.D. number if you already have a Consultant. We also collect information on your purchase (such as date, amount and products).

Our Web sites may also have various clubs, contests, surveys and other events. To join in these activities we typically ask for your name, billing and shipping addresses, e-mail address and telephone numbers. We may ask for other personal information on a voluntary basis. We also have opportunities for you to contact us or a Sales Consultant. Again, we typically ask for your name, billing and shipping addresses, e-mail address and telephone number, plus any comments or questions you may have.

Our Web sites may also provide opportunities for you to e-mail information, such as recipes, club offers, or product information, to a friend. This information is used only to e-mail the desired information, and is not retained by Tupperware.

Our Web sites may also include additional services. Some are provided by third parties (such as Consultant locator services). These services may require information in order to service your needs (such as your address). While we do not control these third parties, we ensure that they are contractually bound to use the information only for authorized purposes. We may also participate in Affiliate programs, which may provide you with additional optional services or benefits.

Use - Information provided via an online purchase will be used to complete your transaction using normal retail methods. Information provided in a purchase, in joining our activities or in requests for information will also be used to contact you with news of our products and opportunities for extra income. If you placed your order through your Consultant's My.Tupperware(SM) Web site, we will provide your Consultant with your name, address, e-mail address and purchase information (date, amount, and products). Your Consultant will not receive your credit card information, and if you opt out of being contacted during the purchase, only your name and purchase information (date, amount and products) will be provided to the Consultant. While our Consultants are independent contractors of our Distributors, they are contractually bound to this Privacy Pledge. Your information may also be combined with the information of others in an aggregated basis, without personally identifying information. This combined information may be used by Tupperware or a third party to guide us in improving our products and services (including our Web sites and catalogs), or for general business purposes (such as forecasting production).

To Opt Out - In certain requests for information there is a box to check if you do not wish to be contacted. If you check it, we will not contact you. In any of our e-mails you receive from Tupperware or a Consultant, there will be instructions for unsubscribing from our contact list. If you ask to be removed, you will be. To unsubscribe now, click here. You may also request to review or change your information by contacting our Customer Care department by e-mail, or mail (at Tupperware U.S., Inc., Attn: Customer Care, P.O. Box 2353, Orlando, FL 32802). To better protect the security and integrity of your information, we also verify identity by requesting your full name, bill to address and e-mail address before granting access or making corrections to your information.

## Our Cookies Don't Bite

"Cookies" are very small text files your Web browser stores on your computer when you visit some Web sites. It is your identification card, and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. It is uniquely yours and can only be read by the site that gave it to you.

Our cookies help make it easier for you to use our Web sites and to help us customize your experience so that we can provide you with the information you need - when and where you need it. A cookie generated by Tupperware.com, for example, allows you to retrieve your Shopping Cart and address information on a return visit. Cookies do not collect this information, nor is your name, address or product information contained within the cookie itself. The cookie simply holds the "key" that, once read by our Web sites, unlocks this information.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can disable cookies on your computer or have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie by indicating this in the preferences or options menu in your browser. But because we rely on cookies to make the shopping experience easier and more tailored to your needs, your browser must be set to accept cookies before you can place an order.

## Data Security is Important to Us

Ensuring security online is an important part of our pledge to respect your privacy. When you place orders for products, we offer the use of a secure server. Tupperware.com uses SSL (secure sockets layer) to protect your credit card information. SSL encrypts all ordering information, such as your name and credit card number, so it can't be read in transit. In addition, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

## Protecting Children is a Priority

We're fully committed to protecting children who access our Web site. We don't knowingly collect any information from children.

## Our Policy Doesn't Apply to Other Web sites

Third party Internet sites and services accessible through Tupperware.com have separate privacy and data collection practices that are beyond our control. While we try to work with third parties who share our views on privacy, we cannot assume responsibility or liability for their independent practices or actions. You're responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. We recommend that you carefully read their privacy policy before agreeing to leave any personal information.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We make an effort to keep your personal information confidential. However, we may be required to disclose your information to the government or third parties under a valid legal request. For example, a criminal investigation or a lawful subpoena may force disclosure. This is true of every business.

## Your Consent

By using our Web site, you agree to let us collect and use information in a manner consistent with the guidelines stated in this policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we will disclose it. We will not use your information in a new way (not described in this current Privacy Pledge) without first providing you with an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent the new uses.

## Questions or Comments

Should you have any further questions or comments about our Privacy Pledge, please contact us at Customer Care.

Effective Date

August 26, 2003
